# Jonathan Choi

**UX + Interaction Designer and glasses wearing enthusiast** 

Phone Number Email Contact 604 704 3122 jonathan\_choi@sfu.ca jonathanchoi.ca

# **Design Experience**

#### **Twitch Feature Design**

3 Weeks in May (School)

#### UX, UI, Interaction Design

Implemented a new Twitch feature to help extend the user's app experience when their followed streamers aren't online following brand and user research

#### Dipp'd Ecommerce Site

Jan - Mar 2021 (School)

#### UX, Interaction Design and Front End Dev

Produced a web and mobile site driven by a self created brand identity amongst a 3 person team to help scale the store's business. Specialized in creating copy and microinteractions within portions of the site

#### **Ventura Future Promotion**

Nov - Dec 2020 (School)

#### UX, Interaction, Graphic Design

Developed graphical and visual assets in a 4 person team to inspire and motivate designers to register for the event. Assisted in forming the art direction, creating copy and making interactions for the prototype

# **Other Experience**

#### **Scouts Leader**

Sept 2018 - Present

Developed teaching plans for meetings in local scouts groups as a volunteer providing an engaging learning experience.

## **GX Representative - PNE**

Aug 2015 - 2019 + Oct 2019

Clarified information involving exhibition features and show times to customers at the PNE. Communicated over the phone and in person to provide engaging and memorable interactions for customers.

# Production Assistant - Stage 49 Ltd.

Aug 2018 - 2019

Collaborated with production and crew members to set up locations for scenes and relay information during filming. Provided flexible assistance throughout the entire day of each shoot.

#### **Career Skills**

#### **Technical Expertise**

Photoshop, InDesign, Illustrator, After Effects, Vegas Pro, Figma, Journey Maps, Personas, Moodboards, Wireframing, Prototyping, HTML, CSS, JS, Copywriting

#### **Interpersonal Abilities**

Teamwork + Collaboration, Leadership, fluency in Cantonese and English

#### **Education**

#### Simon Fraser University

Sept 2019 - Present

Majoring in Interactive Arts and Technology for a Bachelor of Science

#### **Awards/Achievements**

#### SFU Open Scholarship

September 2021

#### Dean's Honour Roll

February 2021

# BC District + Achievement Scholarship

June 2019

### Medal of the Maple Award

April 2018

#### **Interests and Activities**

- Video editing
- Watching eSports
- Everything Star Wars
- · Eating Sushi
- Playing games